Gauri Kale

I am UX designer currently seeking challenging and fulfilling position as a UX/Product Designer where I can utilize my UX design and development skills to bring ideas to life, in a unique and compelling way.

Portfolio: gaukale.com

PROJECTS

<u>Cloud Storage App</u> — Data Box

Designed a user-friendly cloud storage platform to backup, share and create content. Starting with through research, survey and analysis, crafting personas and creating design.

<u>Music Player</u> — Bloc Jams jQuery Project.

Developed existing code to add functionality, and jQuery to insert information into the DOM.

Busy Bus App — Transit App

Created a mobile app called Busy Bus, an application to help commuters to track their ETA.

EDUCATION

Bloc — *Apprenticeship* (2018-2019)

Kaplan University—Associate Science in IT (2007-2008)

Art Institute — *Digital Design Diploma* (2005-2007)

St. Francis School — Bachelor of Arts in Graphic Design (1998-2001)

Experience

Computer Teacher, NI High School, India. (2003 – 2004)

Teaching basic computer skills to students from 5th through 10th grade.

Background Sketching Artist, UTV India. (2001 – 2003)

• For kids' Animated TV series, sketched background scenes on paper.

Freelance Designer (2001 – 2002)

 Designed Brochures, Book Covers and Logos with Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop.



Foster City, CA 913-957-6321

gaukale@gmail.com



SKILLS

Visual Design

UX/UI Design

User Research & Testing

Brand Strategy & Identity

Information Architecture

Personas & User Stories

Wireframing & Prototyping

TOOLS

Adobe Creative Suite

Figma

InVision

Usability Hub

GitHub

Draw.io

LANGUAGES

HTML, CSS, & JavaScript

Java

Visual Basic